const tharu = [
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "अगम",
      options: ["expansive", "weapons", "patience"],
      correctAnswer: "expansive",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "दबिया",
      options: ["dangerous", "khukuri", "pretty"],
      correctAnswer: "khukuri",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question: "खोखा",
      options: ["full", "packet", "empty"],
      correctAnswer: "empty",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question: "खोच",
      options: ["hole", "quarrel", "good"],
      correctAnswer: "quarrel",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "गतेगते",
      options: ["slowly slowly", "fast fast", "date"],
      correctAnswer: "slowly slowly",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "घुची",
      options: ["study", "explore", "pit"],
      correctAnswer: "pit",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "चिन्या",
      options: ["sensetive", "accident", "full"],
      correctAnswer: "accident",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "चुरा",
      options: ["bitten rice", "bangle", "dance"],
      correctAnswer: "bitten rice",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question: "छौरा",
      options: ["small", "boy", "sky"],
      correctAnswer: "boy",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "जरना",
      options: ["firewood", "waterfall", "sea"],
      correctAnswer: "firewood",
    },
  ];
  export default tharu;